🗷 sgchi@purdue.edu | 🏕 engineering.purdue.edu/people/seunggeun.chi.1 | 🖸 sgchi | 🛅 seunggeun-chi-963050153 | 🎓 Seunggeun Chi

## Research Interests\_

My research interests lie in Machine Learning and its applications to real-world problems. Representation Learning in Computer Vision problems is my primary study. My research also spans over Combinatorial Optimization problems which aim to extract rules by applying Reinforcement Learning.

## **Education**

**Purdue University** West Lafayette, U.S.

Ph.D. STUDENT IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2021 - current

• C-Design Lab, Advisor: Karthik Ramani

**Seoul National University** Seoul, S.Korea

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING Mar. 2019 - Aug. 2021

• Optimization Lab, Advisor: ByungRo Moon

**Seoul National University** Seoul, S.Korea Mar. 2013 - Feb. 2019

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING • Computer Architecture Lab, Advisor: SangLyul Min

## Publications & Patents

#### **Conference Proceedings**

- S. Chi\*, H. Chi\*, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. Skeleton-ODE: Learning Representation by Predicting the Future for Online Skeleton-based Action Recognition IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2023, submitted
- [C3] S. Chi\*, H. Chi\*, S. Chan, K. Ramani. Pose Relation Transformer: Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation. IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA), 2023
- [C2] H. Chi, M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022
- [C1] M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Y. Cha, B. R. Moon. Evolution-based Meta Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Optimization. In proceedings of the 23rd The Genetic and Evolutionary Computation Conference (GECCO), 2021

#### **Patent**

• K.Ramani, H.Chi, S.Chi. Pose Relation Transformer And Refining Occlusions For Human Pose Estimation. U.S. Patent Application (MMB 1743-0299P)

### Skills

#### **Research and Development Stacks**

**Major Languages** Python, C/C++, java, Verilog Machine Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow **Computer Vision** OpenCV, OpenGL

Web Languages Nginx, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS

Database MySQL, SQLite

#### Other Tools and Skills

Other Langauges Shell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab, R **Operating Systems** macOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows

Text Editors & IDE Vim, VSCode, Eclipse

> Software SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

> > VCS Git

# **Research & Project**

# Action Diffusion Model: Composing action from text-based input with Diffusion Model

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ. Mar. 2023 -

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

• Aligned motion representation and text representation in the latent space.

- Developed latent diffusion model for effective diffusion process.
- Established novel action composition algorithm.

#### Skeleton-based action sequence generation with salient atomic actions

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

Dec 2022 -

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Encode latent action trajectory with Neural ODE.

- · Extract the salient action frames of actions, and define atomic actions with the salient action frames.
- Apply diffusion model to generate continuous action sequences with atomic actions.

SEUNGGEUN CHI · CURRICULUM VITAE

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

- · formulated malfunctioning cases and defined user-friendly environment
- Developed user-friendly navigation UI
- https://github.com/WICG/spatial-navigation

# Academic Activities \_\_\_\_

#### Reviewer

- The IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023
- Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2023

# Working Experience \_\_\_\_\_

SK Hynix Icheon, S.Korea

INTERN RESEARCHER Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2017

- · Designed an exclusive chip for testing 3D NAND flash architecture and verified the reliabilty of existing architectures
- Developed a module for predicting locality of data and tested it with real data

#### **Korean National Police Agency**

Dokdo, S.Korea
Dec. 2013 - Sep. 2015

AUXILIARY POLICE

# **Teaching Experience**

### **Purdue University**

ME 55300 Product and Process Design, 2023	Teaching Assistant
---	--------------------

## **Seoul National University**

CS.4190.681A	Genetic Algorithm, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.407	Algorithm, 2019-fall, 2020-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.M1522.407	Data Structure, 2019-spring, 2020-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.308	Computer architecture, 2018-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.035.001	<b>Digital Computer Concept and Practice</b> , 2017-fall, 2018-fall	Teaching Assistant
PE.051.004	Volley ball, 2018-fall, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant

# **Honors & Awards**

### Competition of accelerating General-Purpose GPU sponsored by Intel

Manycore Programming Lab

1ST PLACE

Korea Ministry of Science and ICT

## The National Scholarship for Science and Engineering

Noted Millistry of Science and ICT

FULL SCHOLARSHIP

Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2021

# Invited Talk\_\_\_\_\_

Yonsei University Seoul, S.Korea

GUEST LECTURER: REPRESENTATION LEARNING FOR HUMAN ACTION RECOGNITION AND GENERATION

Apr. 2023